3.
Inspiring stories about the Olympic Games
1.
The kind Norwegian There is a cross-country skiing race which is part of the Winter Olympics.
In 2006 a Canadian skier, Sara Renner,
was taking part in the cross-country final when her left pole broke.
This was a serious problem as she needed the pole to help her travel quickly through the deep snow.
So Renner was able to get a silver medal.
The Special Olympic athlete For athlete Eric Williams gold medals are nice,
but good sportsmanship is more important.
In 2005 Eric competed in running races and the long jump.
He said, "I’ve been competing in the Special Olympics ever since I was at high school.
It’s really a good experience.
You get to meet different athletes and volunteers and make all kinds of friends."
John Corbett,
an organizer of the Special Olympics said, "
He always does his best and has a wonderful time in the process.
He truly appreciates (感激) all the people around him who are trying to help,
and he makes that appreciation known."
Let’s hope Eric wins more medals in the next Special Olympics!
At that time he was very ill and in great pain.
Although he had reached the standard for the final of the race he decided at first not to take part.
However, just before the race was going to start he changed his mind.
He ran from his room and arrived at the race track a few minutes
before the race was about to begin.
Surprisingly, he won the race, finishing well ahead of everyone else
and showing what true courage and perseverance (毅力) can achieve.